redcounty.com 2008-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Red County

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the Partisan Media Group, LLC (hereafter referred to as PMG) website, www.redcounty.com.

Because PMG wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. This web site has agreed to notify you of:

  * What personal information of yours is collected from you through the web site
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PMG's control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact customer service at mail@redcounty.com.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
PMG is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. PMG collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

 **PURCHASE**  
PMG requires that information be provided when purchasing PMG  products. This information is used by PMG in the following manner:

Financial information necessary to purchase PMG products includes the customer's name, credit card billing address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. Credit card numbers are not stored or archived by PMG except the last 4 digits of the credit card which are kept as part of the purchase record. The last 4 digits of the credit card are kept in order to assist in future customer inquiries related to the purchase. Shipping information necessary to deliver physical  product includes the customer's name and shipping address. PMG will not use this information to mail any other solicitation nor will PMG sell this information to any third party.

Contact information necessary to identify the customer includes the customer's name and email address. This information is required in order to email a purchase receipt to the customer containing information about the purchase that was made. The email address may also be used to contact the customer regarding problems processing the order. The name and email address are used for security purposes by our customer service personnel with regards to any customer inquiries about a  purchase. Information regarding a customer  purchase will only be provided at the email address used for that purchase. The name and email information may also be used to contact the customer about  products available on our web site. If a customer desires to not be contacted about our  products using their email address, they can prevent the email address from receiving PMG product solicitations. Please see the below policy on 'opt-out' and discontinue.

 **COOKIES**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies by themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you will not be able to purchase  on our web site without session cookies enabled. The cookies allow PMG to manage the state of the order purchase process. Cookies may also be used to store a code that provides the customer with special price offers on PMG products and to determine from which web site a special price offer was made.

 **REFERRERS**  
A Referrer is the information passed along by a web browser that references the Web site that you came to the PMG web site from. This Referrer is automatically collected by our web server. This information is used by PMG to identify broad demographic trends about use of our site. You will not be personally identified by this information.  
 **  
IP ADDRESSES**  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. PMG web sites automatically collect IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information about web site use. PMG will not use your IP address to identify any personal information.

 **SECURITY**  
Information collected by PMG is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. All of our employees are dedicated to maintaining and upholding your privacy and security and are aware of our privacy and security policies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, PMG cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

The PMG web site purchase forms ask users to enter sensitive personal information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our purchase order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

 **SPECIAL OFFERS**  
PMG customers will occasionally receive information on PMG products, services, and special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our opt-out and discontinue policy below.

 **CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
If a customer's personal information changes (such as your email), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal information provided to us. This can be done emailing our Customer Support.

 **OPT-OUT & DISCONTINUE**  
A PMG customer may elect to avoid future communications from PMG by sending us an email at mail@redcounty or selecting Unsubscribe and indicate your email address and request we discontinue future communications. Under urgent circumstances, PMG may be required to send you information about your  purchase, but we will not send you unsolicited communications regarding any commercial offers or advertisements if you have opted out or discontinued communications.

 **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
